John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Office Files
  - Sub-Series A: Consulting
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Billing, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      Work summaries and travel expense vouchers.
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Carnegie Tech, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Convair Development of Qualitative Personnel Requirement Proposal (Box 52, Folder 26)
      Three copies of a proposal to Convair for the the B-58 aircraft.
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Memorandums, 1953-1955 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      Includes requests for reimbursement for out of pocket expenses.
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry and Co.: Sloan Fellows, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      Schedule and confidential evaluations.
    - Henry Spen and Company Reports (Box 52, Folder 30)
      Three reports: Recommendations from Ten Management Men; Training Needs Survey; and Policy and Personnel Recommendations.
    - Westinghouse Key Personnel Search, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      March 31, 1955. Progress report.
    - Contract Proposals, 1953-1954 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      Proposal from the Tufts College Institute for Experimental Psychology.
    - Management Consulting Competition, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      Information on competing firms.
    - Professional Assistance, 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      Correspondence and resume.
    - Promotion of Cornehlsen and Associates, 1958-1970 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      Correspondence and publicity to help win contracts.
    - Prospects File, 1953-1973 (Box 52, Folder 36)
      Correspondence with companies that might be in need of consulting services.
    - Resumes, 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Letters of interest and resumes of persons looking for work as consulting psychologists.
    - Robert Guest Resume (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Two copies and correspondence.
    - Correspondence: A-G, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: G-Z, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - American College Personnel Association Correspondence, 1975-1958 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      General correspondence. Includes report "The Impact of Institutional Size and Complexity Upon Student Personnel Services" by Robert H. Shaffer, Dean of Students, Indiana University
    - American Library Association Correspondence, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      Correspondence mostly regarding consulting for recruiting new librarians.
    - American Management Association, 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - American Personnel and Guidance Association Correspondence, 1975-1958 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - American Psychological Association Correspondence, 1975-1958 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Trainiing Directors Correspondence, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      Letter announcing a December 9, 1958, luncheon meeting.
    - B: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Boeing Airplane Company Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - C: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - N: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Phagan, Tillison and Tremble Correspondence, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      Correspondence with accountant, mostly regarding an employee's salary.
    - ACPA Chicago Meeting, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      Correspondence asking Dr. Cornehlsen to be a commentator at the ACPA Chicago meeting on April 17, 1962.
    - American Society for Trainiing and Development, New York Metropolitan Chapter, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      Correspondence and workshop announcements.
    - Beals: Human Engineering Problems in Training Devices, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      Lynn S. Beals, Jr. Presented at the 57th Annual Convention of the Association of Military Surgeons, November 9-11, 1950.
    - Beals: The General Practice of Training, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      Lynn S. Beals, Jr. Reprint from the Journal of Aviation Medicine, volume 23, pages 271-279, June, 1952.
    - Behavior Modification (Box 53, Folder 23)
      Includes syllabus from Hofstra University's course "Behavior Modification in the Classroom" and case studies from industry.
    - Tests Can't Reveal What Career Is Key to Your Future Success, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      Arthur L. Benson. B'nai B'rith Occupational Brief Series
    - Bibliography Notes (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Bibliography on Factors Related to Attracting Research Scientists to Jobs, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      January 2, 1962. Mahler Associates and Institute of Applied Psychological Research.
    - Book Notes (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Book Notices (Box 53, Folder 28)
      Flyers announcing new book on psychology
    - Bradley: The Work Addict, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      Nelson Bradley. Reprinted from Sales Management, July 7, 1961.
    - Bulletin of the American Youth Commission, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      v.5:no.3 (1941:Mar.). American Council on Education.
    - California Test Bureau: Educational Bulletin, 1945-1948 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      Bulletins 1-5, 7-15, 18.
    - Central Dimensions in Management Processes (Box 53, Folder 32)
      List of 10 management principles.
    - Check List: Day-To-Day Development Practices (Box 53, Folder 33)
      Check list for effective management.
    - Chronicle Guidance Service Posters, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 34)
      Wall calendar, 6 Occupational Briefs, 8 posters.
    - Chronicle Guidance Service Posters, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 35)
      7 article reprints, 6 Occupational Briefs, 8 posters.
    - Civil Service: Announcement of Open Competitive Examination, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 36)
      May 9, 1950. United States Civil Service Commission, Board of U.S. Civil Service Examiners.
    - Clippings, 1958-1970 (Box 53, Folder 37)
      Newspaper and magazine clippings. Mostly from 1958, some undated.
    - College Student Counseling and Guidance Needs (Box 53, Folder 38)
      Two reports from San Francisco State College
    - Continuing Education Courses, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      Proposals for five courses
    - Cornehlsen: Analysis of Executive Potential, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 40)
      Speech for the Pharmaceutical Association, April 16, 1969.
    - Cornehlsen: Development of Leadership Skills, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 41)
      Speech for the AMA Meeting, April 7-8, 1969.
    - Cornehlsen: Proposed Course, Psychological Factors in Interviewing, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 42)
      John H. Cornehlsen. September 28, 1973.
    - Cornehlsen: Talk on "Team Building" (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Cornell: Eleventh Annual Conference of Training Directors: Identification and Assessment of Management Potential, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 44)
      October 22-24, 1957. Cornell Conference Report, sponsored by the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
    - Cox: Have We Moved Ahead, Backward or Does the Situation Remain the Same?, 1938 (Box 53, Folder 45)
      Philip Cox and John C. Duff. Excerpt from "Guidance" textbook.
    - Critical Factors Outline (Box 53, Folder 46)
      Five essential areas to explore for Personnel Assessment
    - Critical Manpower Article (Box 53, Folder 47)
      Source materials and handwritten draft.
    - Cureton: The Principal Compulsions of Factor-Analysts (Box 53, Folder 48)
      Edward E. Cureton. Test Service Notebook no.4
    - A Current Appraisal of the Behavioral Sciences, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 49)
      Supplement to The American Behavioral Scientist, v.7:no.3 (1963:Nov.).
    - Development and Appraisal Workshop (Box 53, Folder 50)
      Notes, instructions, case histories.
    - Development Review (Box 53, Folder 51)
      Blank performance evaluation form.
    - Dill: Strategies for Self-Education, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 52)
      W. R. Dill, W. B. S. Crowston, and E. J. Elton. Reprint from Harvard Business Review, November-December 1965.
    - Drucker on Managing Discontinuity (Box 53, Folder 53)
      Booklet for a BNA film series.
    - Dunnette: Behavioral Science Research and the Conduct of Business, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 54)
      Marvin D. Dunnette and Zita Marie Brown. Reprint from the Academy of Management Journal, v.11:no.2 (1968:June).
    - Dunnette: Compensation: Some Obvious Answers to Unasked Questions, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 55)
      Marvin D. Dunnette. Reprint from Compensation Review, First Quarter 1969.
    - Dunnette: People Feeling: Joy, More Joy, and the "Slough of Despond", 1969 (Box 53, Folder 56)
      Marvin D. Dunnette. Reprint from The Journal of Applied Behavioral Science, v.5:no.1 (1969).
    - Dunnette: Psychological Testing for the Engineering Profession, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 57)
      Marvin D. Dunnette. Presented at the New York Meeting of the American Association for the Advancement f Science, December 29, 1956.
    - EF To Serve You, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 58)
      A prestentaion of the Swedish Management Consultants Ekonomisk Foretagsledning
    - Eckenrode: Human Engineering in the Chemical Industry, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 59)
      Robert T. Eckenrode and Edward J. Welch. Article from Chemical Engineering News, v.31:no.43 (1953:Oct. 26).
    - Excerpts from a book: The "Problems" (Box 53, Folder 60)
      Parts of chapters 5, 7, 9, 10, and 11.
    - Executive Charateristics, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 61)
      List of 30 characteristics from the Harvard Business Review
    - Executive Potential Audit (Box 53, Folder 62)
      Cornehlsen and Strong.
    - Executive Seminar Center, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 63)
      Office of Career Development, U.S. Civil Service Commission.
    - The Executive Study Conference: Issues and Concepts in Executive Education and Development, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 64)
      December 1-2, 1965. Agenda, list of participants, handwritten notes. Includes reprint of Richard S. Barrett's "Impact of the Executive Program on the Participants" from the Journal of Industrial Psychology, v.3:no.1 (1965: Mar.).
    - The Executive Study Conference: The Measurement of Organizational Effectiveness, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 65)
      May 14-15, 196*. Agenda, list of participants, handwritten notes.
    - Executives Wanted (Box 53, Folder 66)
      Handwritten book proposal and outline.
    - Exit Interview, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Experiment on Independent Study, 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 68)
      Second in a series of studies at Antioch College, sponsored by a grant from The Fund for the Advancement of Education (Ford Foundation).
    - Flanagan: Testing in Management Selection: State of the Art, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 69)
      John C. Flanagan and Robert E. Krug. Reprint from Personnel Administration, March-April, 1964.
    - Fleming: Improve Power-Plant Instrumentation By Applying Human-Engineering Data, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 70)
      J. G. Fleming. Article from Power (1954: Jan.).
    - The Fund for the Republic, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 71)
      Letter confirming an interview with Dr. Cornehlsen.
    - GF Workshop Views: Interviewing, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 72)
      January 1957. Personnel Development.
    - Glickman: Factor Analysis of Performance Reports on Navy Junior Officers, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 73)
      April 9, 1954. Albert S. Glickman. Eastern Psychological Association.
    - Gould: Book Review of Take Today: The Executive as Dropout, by Marshall McLuhan and Barrington Nevitt (Box 53, Folder 74)
      Review by Jack Gould.
    - Guidance News: Directory of the Bureau of Educational and Vocational Guidance, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 75)
      v.7:no.5 (1956:June). Board of Education of the City of New York.
    - Handwritten Book Chapters (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Handwritten Notes (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - Harrell: Managers' Performance and Personality, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      September 1959. Thomas W. Harrell, Stanford University, Graduate School of Business.
    - Harvard Career Counseling Conference, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      October 9, 1956. Letter and attendance list
    - Harvard Graduate School Career Office, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Correspondence.
    - Harvard: The Use of Resumes in Alumni Placement, 1953-1954 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      Also includes "Bulletin: Alumni Placement Procedure" and a blank placement application form.
    - Homan: Wash Your Hands, Damn It!, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      William E. Homan. Photocopy of an article from New York Times Magazine, March 7, 1971.
    - Hurns: Management Inventory and Development, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Thomas E. Hurns. Talk given before the Industrial Relations Committee of the Edison Electric Institute, June 4, 1951.
    - Hymes: Behavior and Misbehavior, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      James L. Hymes, Jr.
    - Intercollegiate Bibliography: Cases in Business Administration, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      v.8 (1963:Apr.). Compiled by Grace V. Lindfors.
    - Jacobs: Biophysiologic Development and Evaluation of Intelligence, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      Lewis Jacobs and Jean Jacobs. Reprint for New York State Journal of Medicine, v.71:no.13 (1971: July).
    - Jenkins: Efficiency of the Jenkins Global Personality Inventory, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      Thomas N. Jenkins. Reprinted from Journal of Psychological Studies, v.13:no.1 (1962).
    - Jenkins: The Second Order Components of Human Personality, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      Thomas N. Jenkins. Reprinted from Journal of Psychological Studies, v.12:no.6 (1961).
    - Johnson: Validity and Test-Retest Stability of the Nash Managerial Effectiveness Scal on the Revised Form of the Strong Vocational Interest Blank, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      James C. Johnson and Marvin D. Dunnette. Reprint from Personnel Psychology, v.21:no.3 (1968: Autumn).
    - Kellogg: The Mathematics of Management, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      Paul Kellogg. An address.
    - Kellogg: Sales Promotion Profits and Mathematics, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      Paul Kellogg. An address before the Technical Advertisers Association of Montreal, February 14, 1945..
    - Made to Measure, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      January 31 - February 2, 1951. Notes from a Conference on Personnel Measurement. Employee Relations Department, Standard Oil Company (New Jersey)
    - Maier: The Quality of Group Decisions as Influenced by the Discussion Leader, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      Norman R. F. Maier. Reprint from Human Relations, v.3:no.2 (1950: June).
    - A Management Audit: National Gypsum Company, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      Special Audit no.100 by The Corporate Director.
    - Managing Ineffective People (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Mead: Human Engineering: The Study of the Human Factor in Machine Design, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      Leonard C. Mead and Joseph W. Wulfeck. Reprint from The Scientific Monthly, v.75:no.6 (1952: Dec.).
    - Methods of Training Teachers (Box 54, Folder 20)
      Mostly handwritten notes.
    - Motivating People: Money Isn't Everything, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      Photocopy of an article from Newsweek, April 22, 1968.
    - Motivational Studies, 1952-1953 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      Correspondence regarding motivation in television advertising.
    - Myers: Conditions for Manager Motivation, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      M. Scott Myers. Reprint from Harvard Business Review, January-February 1966.
    - Myers: Who Are Your Motivated Workers?, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      M. Scott Myers. Reprint from Harvard Business Review, January-February 1964.
    - National Training Laboratories: Seleceted Reading Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      June 1962 and June 1963. Grouped by subject. The 1962 list is nine pages and has eight different subjects. The 1962 list is only two pages and seven subjects.
    - News clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      Articles on executive burnout and sensitivity training.
    - Notes on Bass, Chapter 7: Industrial Organization (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Office of Naval Research, London: Engineering Psychology in England, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      Techinal Report ONRL-52-56. American Embassy, London, England.
    - Office of Naval Research, London: Measurement of Perceptual Phenomena By Ekman and Johannson, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      Techinal Report ONRL-28-56. American Embassy, London, England.
    - Office of Naval Research, London: Recent Developments in Experimental Psychology in Austria, Southern Germany, and Switzerland, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      Techinal Report ONRL-25-57. American Embassy, London, England.
    - Office of Naval Research, London: Research at Geneva on Intellectual Development, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      Techinal Report ONRL-120-55. American Embassy, London, England.
    - "Outreach": An Approach to Human Relations in the Introductory Psychology Course, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      September 3, 1966. Report of a Symposium given at the American Psychological Association Convention
    - Perris: Shorter Hours and Time Study, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      Norris M. Perris. An address at a meeting of The Society of Methods Engineers, January 17, 1945.
    - Personnel Evaluation (Box 54, Folder 34)
      Handwritten notes, reports, charts. Includes typescript reports.
    - Personnel Psychology Applied, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      Tentative chapter outlines.
    - The PERT Approach (Box 54, Folder 36)
      Photocopy of a book chapter.
    - Peteson: Testing for the Professions: Dentistry, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      Shailer Peterson. Presented at the New York Meeting of the American Association for the Advancement f Science, December 29, 1956.
    - Report to the President from Chairman, Civil Service Commission, on Executive Seminar Center, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 38)
      July 22, 1965. Press release.
    - Research Study (Box 54, Folder 39)
      Statistical breakdown of academic year 1946-1947 student boby.
    - Rewards of Work (Box 54, Folder 40)
      Excerpts from Organizational Psychology
    - Rogers: "Client-Centered" Psychotherapy, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      Carl R. Rogers. Reprint from Scientific American, November 1952.
    - SRA: Self-Scorer Tests (Box 54, Folder 42)
      Ira S. Glick. Press release.
    - Sales Attitudes, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      Correspondence and blank Inventory of Salesmen's Attitudes forms.
    - Scarf: The Man Who Gave Us "Inferiority Complex," "Compensation," "Overcompensation," "Aggressive Drive," and "Style of Life", 1971 (Box 54, Folder 44)
      Maggie Scarf. Photocopy of an article from New York Times Magazine, February 28, 1971.
    - Selecting Company Executives, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 45)
      National Industrial Conference Board Studies in Personnel Policy, no.161.
    - Selection Requirements for Volunteer Duties, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 46)
      February 1945. Supplement to Selection Requirements Manual for Types of Naval Officer Duty, NavPers 16407.
    - Smith: Six Basic Factors in Handwriting Classification, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 47)
      Theodora LeH. Smith. Reprint from The Journal of Criminal Law, Criminology and Police Science, v.44:no.6 (1954: Mar./Apr.).
    - Smith: Questions the Business Leader Should Ask Himself, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 48)
      George Albert Smith, Jr.. Reprint from Harvard Business Review, March-April 1956.
    - Social and Personal Diagnosis (Box 54, Folder 49)
    - The Socio-Guidrama Series (Box 54, Folder 50)
      Listing of 10-minute guidance playlets to help young people with their problems.
    - Some Data on Reliability and Validity of the Accounting Tests (Box 54, Folder 51)
    - Standards for Use in Preparing and Evaluating Occupational Literature, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 52)
      Publications Committee, Occupational Research Division. Reprint from Occupations, the Vocational Guidance Journal, February 1950.
    - Stanford Reading Center: Reading Survey, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 53)
      November 2, 1939.
    - State or District Conventions of State Teachers' Associations, Fall 1956 thru Spring 1957 (Box 54, Folder 54)
      May 10, 1956. State Teachers Magazine.
    - Stevenson, Jordan and Harrison: Profit on Net Worth: Continuing the Analysis of the Profit Structure, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 55)
      Monograph no.2.
    - Stevenson, Jordan and Harrison: The Scientific Approach to Effective Personnel Control, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 56)
      Promotional literature. Includes "Additional Services Available Through the Psychological Division of Stevenson, Jordan and Harrison."
    - Strategy of Fob Finding, 1955-1970 (Box 54, Folder 57)
      Handwritten notes, S. John Loscocco's "Case History of a Job Hunter", Allen R. Dodd, Jr.'s "Joh Hunter: The Diary of a Lost Year", Executive Register's "How To Change Your Position", and Kenneth R. Adler's "Pathway to Your Future".
    - Stryker: How Executives Get Jobs, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 58)
      Perrin Stryker. Photocopy from Fortune, August 1953.
    - A Study of Company AO Now and Company AO of the Future (Box 54, Folder 59)
      An organizational study of Heppenstall Steel, which includes Midvale Steet.
    - The Teacher's Letter, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 60)
      February 5, 1955.
    - Tektronix Coaching Manual, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 61)
      TEP Course no.8.01.
    - Terman Talk (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - Test Service Bulletin, 1955-1967 (Box 54, Folder 63)
      The Psychological Corporation. no.48 (1955: Jan.) and no.57 (1967: May).
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: Understanding Testing: Purposes and Interpretations for Pupil Development, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 64)
      OE-25003
    - U. S. Department of Labor: Employment Test Validation, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 65)
      Memorandum concerning Executive Order 11246.
    - Union Carbide: Oral Communication Workshop, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 66)
      January 11-12, 1971. Agenda, suggested reading, director's guide, exercises.
    - Who's Who in Training and Development, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 67)
      Official Membership Directory of the American Society for Training and Development.
    - Why People Work (Box 54, Folder 68)
      Handwritten notes and overhead transparencies.
    - Xerox: Screening Handbook for Project Step-Up: An Approach to the Measurement of Motivation in the Culturally Disadvantaged, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 69)
      Xerox Corporation. Includes blank interview form and Ruben Krigsman's "Motivation of the Disadvantaged Negro".
    - Yeshiva University: Films on Business and Industry, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 70)
      Special Film List, Revised Edition no.1, December 1963.
  - Sub-Series B: Teaching
    - BES 670: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 71)
      One course evaluation with a personal note from the student.
    - BSA 616: Organizational Behavior [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 72)
      Handwritten notes and printed resources.
    - BSA 616: Organizational Behavior [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - BSA 616: Course Evaluations, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 74)
      Evaluation forms filled in by students.
    - BSA 616: Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - BSA 670: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Corporate Personnel Development: College Recruiting Interviewing, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 77)
      January 1967. Handout
    - Education 808: Changing Classroom Behavior (Box 54, Folder 78)
      Bibliography and handwritten notes.
    - Education 808: Behavior Management in the Classroom [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 54, Folder 79)
    - Education 808: Behavior Management in the Classroom [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Education 808: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Interview Training: Lecture Notes (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Printed notes and resources.